Will Sentance: 假设我们有这个应用程序，它将每个用户存储在我的应用程序中
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's say we have this
application storing each user in my app
他们各自的数据。
with their respective data.
让我们保持简单。
Let's keep it really simple.
我们已经有了大量的数据和用户。
We already have lots of data and
lots of users.
简单一点，用户名 Tim,
Keep it really simple, user1 name Tim,
用户2名斯蒂芬妮，得分3，得分5。
user2 name Stephanie, score 3, score 5.
我需要为每个用户提供的功能,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The functionality
I need to have for each user, again,
简化只是增加的能力，以增加一个分数的用户,
simplify just the ability to increment
to increase the scores user by one,
对不起，对不起，用户得分是1。
sorry, sorry, user score by one.
事实上，这里有很多功能。
In fact,
there'd be a ton of functionality here.
现在，有两件事情，我不想运行我的代码或秋天的所有
Now, two things, I do not want to have
to run all over my fall of code or
我的代码的瀑布，尝试和猎取增量函数。
my falls of code to try and
hunt out that increment function.
在我的理想世界里，user1在我的任何地方
In my ideal world, wherever user1 is in my
现在正在传递到我的应用程序的不同位,
application right now being passed around
into different bits of my application,
我在它旁边有一个增量功能。
I have that increment functionality
right there adjacent to it.
最理想的情况是，它几乎被规定为
And ideally, it's somehow pretty
much prescribed to only be
适用于 user1数据或 user2，以及 user2数据和
applicable to the user1 data or
to the user2, and to the user2 data and
而不是突然想要申请我的主桌。
not suddenly gonna be tried
to apply to my lead table.
我要尝试增加我的铅表，通常是这样的。
I'm going to try to increment
my lead table, normally a thing.
是的，所以我怎么能捆绑在一个包在一种
Yeah, so how could I bundle up
in one package in one kind of
组织数据结构，数据与功能所以
organizing data structure,
that data with the functionality so
我知道他们就在彼此身边。
I know that they're right
there next to each other.
我甚至可以使用一个特殊的，威尔 · 森特斯: 点,
And I can even use a special,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Dot,
点也许是为了使用该数据的功能。
[LAUGH] dot perhaps in order to use
the functionality on that data.
如何将功能和数据捆绑到一个地方？
How can I bundle functionality and
data in one place?
Braden 你有什么主意吗？
Braden, you got any idea?
说话人2: 在物体或公共汽车上。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In object or bus.
威尔 · 句子: 在一个物体中，存储在物体中。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In an object,
store in object.
让我们暂时保持简单。
Let's keep it even simple for now.
存储在对象中，这是完全正确的。
Store in an object, that's exactly right.
因此，对象存储函数及其相关数据。
So objects store functions
with their associated data.
这并不是完全在 JavaScript 中实现的。
This is, well, not fully strictly
implemented in JavaScript.
这就是封装的概念。
This is the notion of encapsulation.
它的意思是保护和捆绑在一个地方，功能和
It's saying protect and
bundle up in one place, functionality and
它所应用的数据，它所应用的数据，[ INAUDIBLE ]语法,
the data that it applies to, the data to
which it applies, [INAUDIBLE] grammar,
它应用于一个小捆绑包中的其他数据。
other data to which it applies
in one little bundle package.
这将改变我们思考代码的方式。
And it's gonna transform how
we can reason about code.
看看这个，我的100,000行代码周围没有搜索,
Look at this, no hunting all
around my 100,000 lines of code,
我的递增函数，我简单地把点放在这里。
my increment function,
I literally just put dot and there it is.
我们今天所做的一切努力,
And it's gonna turn out everything
that we try and do today,
我们今天所做的一切，都是为了达到我的最佳位置。
everything we try and do today,
getting into my optimal position.
我们今天所做的一切都是为了我能成功吗？
Everything we try and do today is really
just gonna be about can I achieve this?
我能在相关数据上实现运行功能吗？
Can I achieve running functionality
on the pertinent data?
不是其他数据，不是随机的测试问题，不是随机的排名表，而是
Not other data, not random quiz questions,
not randomly league tables, but
用户的数据，而不必去寻找功能。
on the user ones data and
not have to go hunt for the functionality.
但它就在那里。
But it's right there.
我把点和控制台,
I put dot and in the console,
我甚至可以看到预先填写的增量，为我预测的。
I'd even see the increment kinda
pre-filled for me, predicted for me.
这就是为我的数据找到相关功能的容易程度。
That's how easy it will be to find
the pertinent functionality for my data.
这就是我的目标。
That's my goal.
你知道吗，我就是在这里做的。
Well, you know what, I did it here.
我在这里完成了。
I did it here, done.
我的思维模式已经完成了。
My paradigm's done.
我得到了数据、功能和一个对象。
I got data, functionality,
and an object done.
但是让我们继续创建对象，因为它会变成
But let's keep creating objects
cuz it's gonna turn out
我们很快就会厌倦这些东西的笔迹。
that we're gonna very quickly get
tired of handwriting these objects.
但是让我们做几次。
But let's do it a few times.
在这样做的同时,
And in doing so,
还要熟悉一些创建对象的不同方法。
also get familiar with a few different
ways to go about creating objects.
人们能想到另一种方法吗？
Can people think of another way?
这里我创建了一个对象，字面上叫做完全填充对象，并且
Here I've created an object, literally
call it the full populate object, and
我已经预先填充了它的所有值。
I've prefilled all its values.
我能做些什么呢？
What can I do instead?
如果我只创建一个空对象 Braden,
If I would just create an empty object,
Braden,
后来我怎样才能给它添加属性呢？
how could I add properties
to it afterwards?
讲者2: 组织一个班级。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Make a class.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 不，只要保持简单就好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
just keep it really simple.
怎么了，马特？
Yeah, Matt?
说话人2: 使用点运算符。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Use a dot operator.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没错，点符号，就是这个。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Exactly,
dot notation, there it is.
使用点符号创建 user2。
Creating user2 with dot notation.
用点表示法声明空属性。
Declare empty properties
with dot notation.
我们开始吧。
Let's get going through.
我只是想确保我们在互动方面达成共识
I just wanna make sure that we're all
on the same page with our interaction
用物体。
with objects.
好的，托德，第一行，我们要在全局内存中保存什么？
Okay, Todd, line one here,
what are we saving in global memory?
说话人2: 你把 user2这个概念定义为一个空对象。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You are defining
the concept user2 as an empty object.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，一个又大又旧的空物体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
big old empty object.
这不是一个真正的东西，只是一个空的对象。
That's not really a thing,
just an empty object.
就是它，一个又大又旧的空物体，分配给它什么财产，托德？
There it is, big old empty object,
assigning what property to it, Todd?
演讲者2: 下一行分配名称。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The next line assigns name.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，并且赋予这个属性什么价值？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, and
assigning what value to that property?
讲者二: 十位。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Ten.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，对不起，[听不见] ，所以
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
sorry, [INAUDIBLE], so
他们称之为键值。
they call these different things,
key value.
我很少在专业代码中听到这样的措辞。
I rarely hear that phrasing
in professional code.
我们倾向于称它为属性名，然后是属性值，好的。
We would tend to call it property name,
and then the property value so, okay.
下一个是 scores 和6。
Next one is score and 6.
然后，马特，我们在最后一张幻灯片上做什么？
And then, Matt,
what are we doing in the last slide here?
我们还要增加一处房产,
We're adding another property, yeah,
我们怎么称呼对象的函数，Matt，各位？
what do we tend to call functions
on objects, Matt, everyone?
讲者二: 方法 威尔 · 森特斯: 方法，是的，做得好,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Method.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Method, yeah, well done,
没错，方法，干得好，伙计们。
exactly, method, well done, folk.
[ INAUDIBLE ] ，就是这个，它把所有的代码都存储起来了。
[INAUDIBLE], there it is, and that's
taking all of its code and storing it.
像往常一样，我们不运行代码，但是
And as usual,
we're not running that code but
我们把整个函数定义从单词 function
we are taking that entire function
definition from the word function to
结束曲括号存储在那个物体上，美丽
closing curly brace storing
on that object, beautiful